<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2023-03-26 00:00:00 +0000 UTC on MyArchieve</title><link>http://localhost:1313/date/2023-03-26-000000-+0000-utc/</link><description>Recent content in 2023-03-26 00:00:00 +0000 UTC on MyArchieve</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/date/2023-03-26-000000-+0000-utc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid><description>Kaptan İslam A. CYBER SECURITY RESEARCHER As a passionate high school student with a strong desire to pursue a career in cybersecurity, I have dedicated myself to working on web application security. Additionally, I improve my skills in both frontend and backend web development. With a keen interest in OSINT, I am expanding my knowledge and developing new skills in this area. I am passionate about sharing my knowledge and experience through blogging and I like to challenge with myself.</description></item><item><title>Archieve</title><link>http://localhost:1313/archieve/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/archieve/</guid><description>Explore my list of published posts in the Archieve. Organized by year and month, it’s easy to find the content you’re looking for. Whether you’re a new reader or a long-time follower, we hope you’ll enjoy discovering new insights and perspectives. Happy reading!
Categories Projects Links Sitemap 2022 April Siber Güvenliğe Nereden Başlamalıyım – Rehber April 23, 2022 TryHackMe: Introductory Researching — CTF Writeup [TR] April 23, 2022 TryHackMe: Tutorial — CTF Writeup [TR] April 23, 2022 Where to Start Cyber-Security - Guide April 23, 2022 OverTheWire: Bandit — Wargames Writeup [TR] April 23, 2022 TryHackMe: Agent T — CTF Writeup [TR] April 23, 2022 TryHackMe: Hacker Methodology — CTF Writeup [TR] April 23, 2022 TryHackMe: OpenVPN — CTF Writeup [TR] April 23, 2022 TryHackMe: Starting Out in Cyber Sec — CTF Writeup [TR] April 23, 2022 TryHackMe: Welcome — CTF Writeup [TR] April 23, 2022 March TryHackMe ile Sıfırdan Zirveye Ulaşma Rehberi [70 Ücretsiz Oda] March 23, 2022 Kelimelerden Ziyade Boşluklara Odaklanmak March 14, 2022 February Python Uygulama Örnekleri ve Notları February 12, 2022 2018 March Programming – [Guide] March 23, 2018 Yazılım – [Rehber] March 23, 2018 İngilizce – [Rehber] March 23, 2018 what the hell March 23, 2018</description></item><item><title>Categories</title><link>http://localhost:1313/categories/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/categories/</guid><description> Dil 1 post Guide 1 post Ingilizce 1 post Kişisel-Gelişim 1 post Overthewire 1 post Programming 1 post Python 1 post Rehber 5 posts Technology 1 post Tryhackme 6 posts Web 1 post Yazılım 3 posts</description></item><item><title>Links</title><link>http://localhost:1313/links/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/links/</guid><description>Yes, I am a criminal. My crime is that of curiosity. My crime is that of judging people by what they say and think, not what they look like. My crime is that of outsmarting you, something that you will never forgive me for.
Blogs Network23 Kllanıcıların kendi web sitelerini ve bloglarını oluşturmalarına izin veren ücretsiz bir hosting hizmetidir. Ayrıca insanların bilgi paylaşmasına, görüşlerini ifade etmesine ve çevrimiçi topluluklarla etkileşimde bulunmasına olanak sağlar.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid><description>Here you can find a collection of all my past and current projects. Each project showcases my skills in web development, Cyber Security, tools and other areas. I hope you enjoy browsing through my work and learning more about my experience and capabilities.
Deneme-1-olmalı Date: March 30, 2023 Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript A description of my new projectA description of my new projectA description of my new projectA description of my new project</description></item></channel></rss>